

# **Shahzaib Rehman**

## Software Engineer

#### **About Me**

I bring a unique blend of technical expertise and creativity to every project. Whether you need a web application, smart contract, DApp, or blockchain-based solution, I am committed to delivering top-quality work that meets your needs and exceeds your expectations. So why wait? Contact me today to see how I can help take your blockchain project to the next level!

## **Professional Experience**

**Cybernest** - Blockchain Developer

Dec 2022 - Present

Exp: 6-Months

Key responsibilities:

- Developed a HRM project for the management of company.
- Created a Smart Contract for Client to Support their NFT marketplace and also developed UI in react for the demo.
- Worked on a DEX that allows different companies to get registered, create their own ERC-20 token and also let registered companies to initiate ICOs.
- Worked on Hyperledger Fabric that allows users to save their Wallets private-keys, Important Documents and add Guardians
- Worked on YouSound project which is a music & shopping experience powered by verified artists & brands.

**Aquila360** - Associate Software Engineer

Dec 2021 - Dec 2022

Exp: 1-Year

Key responsibilities:

- Worked on Security Management System project (SaaS) which had functionalities to manage shifts, duty assignment, attendance, schedule duties
- I was responsible for handling the Server side development.
- Worked on NFT marketplace using ERC-721 standard. The marketplace had functionalities like Minting, buying, selling, auctioning and staking to receive custom ERC-20 tokens as reward.
- Along with development and research, I also have experience with Cloud like Azure. During the tenure I deployed projects including front-end/back-end applications using CI/CD methods.
- These deployments where done using technologies like Docker,
  Kubernetes and writing yaml files for pipelines.

#### **Spyresync** - Software Enigneer Intern

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Exp: 3-Months

Key responsibilities:

- Worked for In house Project Management System project.
- I was responsible for creating the UI on react and configuring python based APIs.
  - Developed Collectables NFT Smart Contracts on ETH and BSC
- Developed Decentralized Banking Application on deployed on Polygon (Mumbai) test network.

## **My Contact**

shahzaibrehman40@gmail.com

+923134766457

Model Town, Lahore, Pakistan

# https://github.com/shahzaibrehman123

### **Hard Skill**

- Smart contract programming (Solidity)
- Defi (Flash Loans, staking, Escrow)
- Tokenomics (Fungible / NFTs)
- Web3 Testing frameworks (Truffle, Mocha, Chai, hardhat)
- Cloud (Azure, Aws)
- DevOps tools ( Docker , Kubernetes)
- MERN Stack
- MongoDB , Firebase

## **Soft Skill**

- Continuous learning
- Resilience
- · Critical thinking
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- University Of Lahore, Defense Campus Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering
   Completed in 2021
- Divisional Public College
  The intermediate of Computer Science (ICS)
  - Completed in 2017